https://palmbeachplasticsurgery.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy - |
E-COURSES
Newsletter
X
Newsletter [Lightbox]
RECEIVE MONTHLY NEWS & PROMO OFFERS!
Schedule a Free Consultation TodayPhone Number: (561) 833-4122
BII Warriors
Breast Implant Explantation (En Bloc)
Anaplastic Large Cell Lymphoma / BIA-ALCL
Breast Implant Removal Surgeon
Breast Removal, Explant Surgery, Total Capsulectomy, and En Bloc
Procedures
Mini / In-Office Plastic Surgery Procedures
The Awake Lift™ (Mini Facelift)
Mini Facelift aka Band Aid Lift Procedure
Mini Cheek Lift (Bandaid Mini-Cheeklift)
Fraxel® Laser Treatment
Laser Photo Rejuvenation (IPL)
Breast Procedures
Breast Implant Explantation (En Bloc)
Breast Implant Illness
Breast Enlargement
Breast Lift
Breast Reduction
Male Breast Reduction (Gynecomastia)
Body Procedures
Arm Lift (Brachioplasty)
News & Articles
Contact Us Today!
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
What information do we collect?
We collect information from you when you fill out a form for us to contact you, send you information or register for one of our events. When requesting information on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, email address, phone number, comments and other information such as your location if you are filling out a contact request. If you are registering for one of our paid events, additional information such as payment information is collected securely to confirm your registration. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.
What do we use your information for?
Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:
To contact you about our Services: Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.
To send periodic emails: The email address you provide, will only be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order, potential order, or information or contact request. Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.
Do we use cookies?
We or 3rd party services we use to track web site activity may store “cookies” on your computer when you visit our website. This allows us and/or the service to recognize your computer the next time you visit us.
The type of information we collect as a result of a cookie is specific to your computer and may include the Internet Protocol (IP) address, the date and time you access our website and what parts of the website are visited. We collect this information to monitor the usage and usefulness of our website and for statistical purposes. You may set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie or to refuse receiving it.
This website uses Google Analytics.
This website uses Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. (“Google”). Google Analytics uses “cookies”, which are placed on your computer, to help us analyze how users use the site. The information generated by the cookie about your use of the website (including your IP address) will be transmitted to and stored by Google on servers in the United States. Google will use this information for the purpose of evaluating your use of the website, compiling reports on website activity for website operators and providing other services relating to website activity and internet usage. Google may also transfer this information to third parties where required to do so by law, or where such third parties process the information on Google’s behalf. Google will not associate your IP address with any other data held by Google. You may refuse the use of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings on your browser, however please note that if you do this you may not be able to use the full functionality of this website. By using this website, you consent to the processing of data about you by Google in the manner and for the purposes set out above.
This website uses Google AdWords, Remarketing, Bing Ads and potentially other online advertising services.
This website uses Google AdWords and its remarketing capability to advertise on third party websites (including Google) to previous visitors to our site. This allows us to advertise to previous visitors who may or may not have completed a task on our site, for example registering for one of our training events. This could be in the form of an advertisement on the Google search results page, or a site in the Google Display Network. Third-party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on someone’s past visits to our website. Any data collected will be used in accordance with our own privacy policy and Google’s privacy policy.
You can set preferences for how Google advertises to you using the Google Ad Preferences page, and if you want to you can opt out of interest-based advertising entirely by cookie settings or permanently using a browser plugin.
We may also use other 3rd party remarketing services and/or other online advertising services such as Bing Ads, Facebook, LinkedIN, etc.
Do we disclose any information to outside parties?
Information you provide to us is not sold or shared with third parties that are not part of our web site or our business. Information about our clients is used and may be shared with our corporate office and staff as well as any stated event partners or event sponsors in the case of an event registration.
Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance
We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.
Your Consent
By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.
Changes to our Privacy Policy
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page. This policy was last modified on May 21, 2014.
Contacting Us
If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information on our Contact Us page or elsewhere on this Web Site.
Real Patients, Real Reviews
Absolutely with no reserve the best experience I have ever had at at Doctors office. Dr. Barr is the most charming man EVER!!!!!! He is an awesome surgeon and did my mini face lift with love and humor, I cant even say what a fantastic job that he did with no pain, the results are what I have been dreaming of!!!! He did the whole thing with Lidocaine injections and I did not feel a thing!!!! The office staff, Pam, LaDonna, Penny, Carla and Dr. Barr’s awesome Nurse Candy made me feel like I was their best friends, Would I go there again, I definitely plan to and I would never go to another Surgeon, I love them all and thank them for their concern and kindness!!!!!!
~ Marie Anteni
Dr. Barr and his staff are extremely pleasant and professional. The office setting is comfortable and everyone is helpful and informative. Dr. Barr is very gracious and skilled and he listens to his patients in a truly caring manner. I highly recommend this group if you want personalized and proficient care. All medical practices could take a cue from the way Dr. Barr makes each patient feel special.
~ Lynne
Excellent and professional ! Ethan happy with the services procured by Dr Barr and his staff
~ Daniele
It has been one week since my mini facelift with Dr. Barr. I am absolutely ecstatic about the result!! I feel fabulous!!! Dr. Barr is an amazing artist and person. His calm manner made me feel comfortable throughout the entire experience.Also, he personally called me two days in a row to see how I was. Dr. Barr’s staff is also amazing!! They are available 24/7 for any questions you might have. I highly recommend Dr. Barr and am willing to share my before and after photos with anyone who is contemplating the min- lift
~ Phyllis G.
Dr. Barr is a perfectionist ..He did a mini facelift on me an it came out exactly the way I thought it would. I was referred by a client to him and it was the best decision I made. Thank you so much.
~ Chris Niewolak
Best ever Doctor and staff!! Highly recommend!
~ Paula G.
Dr. Barr is the best.
~ Angela
Dr Barr and his staff r the best. I’m a big baby and they always make me feel relaxed and calm.
~ Barbara P.
Everyone was professional and caring! Could not have asked for a better experience! Thanks to everyone for a job well done!
~ Annette S.
Always professional and welcoming. Results were beyond my expectations!
~ Elizabeth
I have had great experiences and results with Dr Barr
~ Cindy
I believe that every patient want their doctor to be a genius. Dr Barr truly is a genius. He creates results that are natural and beautifully suited to the patient. In addition to his technical and creative talents, he is also a warm and compassionate individual who treats the patient with patience and kindness and who strives to tailor each treatment to the specific patient. I am thankful to the friend who recommended Dr Barr and to Dr Barr for giving me back my youth.
~ Valued P.
Truly happy. What more can anyone say when you improve their looks!
~ Michelle
This is my second mini face lift with Dr. Barr. I could go anywhere but Dr. Barr is the only doctor I trust with my face! Excellent doctor who produces excellent results.
~ Elizabeth H.
Excellent and competent doctor. Very professional. Wonderful and caring staff. Thanks to all of you .
~ Danièle T.
Enjoy the convenience of PGA location, would prefer better lighting. Staff and Dr. Barr are terrific, always make one feel comfortable.
~ Donna
As a leader in Cosmetic and Reconstructive Surgery industry, Dr. Barr is known as “the Physician that Physicians consult.” Dr. Barr is an active member of the American Society of Plastic Surgery as well as the American Society of Aesthetic Plastic Surgery, and has been in private practice in West Palm Beach for thirty years. It is for these reasons, combined with Dr. Barr and his staff’s extensive skills and experience, that Palm Beach Plastic & Cosmetic Surgery is a premier choice for those pursuing renewal in both beauty and spirit.
~ Darla from Palm Beach
Questions or Want to Schedule an Appointment? Click to Call (561) 833-4122
Contact Us
Palm Beach Plastic and Cosmetic Surgery
1411 N. Flagler Dr., Suite 5800
West Palm Beach,
FL 33401
Phone: (561) 833-4122
Palm Beach Plastic and Cosmetic Surgery
Palm Beach Gardens,
FL 33418
Phone: (561) 200-3385
Site Logo
Plastic & Cosmetic Surgery Links
Mini Procedures
Body Procedures
Skin Procedures
Face Procedures
Breast Procedures
Business Hours Monday to Friday 9:00AM – 5:00PM
At Palm Beach Plastic & Cosmetic Surgery, we view Plastic Surgery procedures in a direct and honest manner using the principles of either addition, subtraction or a combination of both.
We're Online. Let's Stay Connected.
Disclaimer
Privacy Policy
Sitemap
© 2018 - 2020 . All Rights Reserved. Powered by: Web Promotion Partners
West Palm Beach Plastic Surgery and Plastic Surgeon Location
Breast Implant Explantation (En Bloc)
Anaplastic Large Cell Lymphoma / BIA-ALCL
Breast Implant Removal Surgeon
Breast Removal, Explant Surgery, Total Capsulectomy, and En Bloc
Procedures
Mini / In-Office Plastic Surgery Procedures
The Awake Lift™ (Mini Facelift)
Mini Facelift aka Band Aid Lift Procedure
Mini Cheek Lift (Bandaid Mini-Cheeklift)
Laser Photo Rejuvenation (IPL)
Breast Implant Explantation (En Bloc)
Breast Implant Illness
Breast Enlargement
Breast Lift
Breast Reduction
Male Breast Reduction (Gynecomastia)
Body Procedures
Arm Lift (Brachioplasty)
Contact Us Today!
